

### **My Contact**

yalsizhasan@gmail.com

+90 551 064 53 70

istanbul, Turkey

https://github.com/hasanyalsiz

https://hasanyalsiz.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hasanyalsiz/

### **Hard Skill**

- HTML,HTML5
- CSS,SASS,SCSS
- JavaScript,TypeScript
- React,Redux,Thunk,Toolkit
- UI/UX Design(Figma)
- Responsive Design
- Development Tools
- Web Standards and Browser Compatibility
- WordPress
- OpenCart

### **Soft Skill**

- Creativity
- User Focus
- Communication Skills
- Problem solving
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- Turkey, Fatih Sultan Mehmet University Software Specialist Completed in 2023
- Turkey, Dicle University
  Master of Educational Sciences
  Completed in 2017

# **HASAN YALSIZ**

Software Developer Front-End Developer React Developer

#### **About Me**

I am a dynamic and creative frontend developer and passionately write my codes.. I have a strong sense of visual aesthetics and enjoy working with modern web technologies. I am experienced in designing and developing user-friendly interfaces. I am adaptable to teamwork and capable of managing project processes. I am constantly open to learning and self-improvement. I am quite successful in my stress management.

## **Professional Experience**

JuniusTech | Front-End Developer | React Developer 2023-01.04.2024

- Front-end designs were made with HTML, CSS,JS and React.
- Contributed to the work as a team and individually.
- Work was carried out on real-time projects

MimCode | Front-End Developer | React Developer 2021 - 2023

- Front-end designs were made with HTML, CSS,JS and React.
- Versioning was done with Git/Github.
- Contributed to the work as a team and individually.
- I am actively engaged in developing an e-commerce website, contributing to its ongoing enhancements and improvements.
- User-friendly interfaces were designed and continuously improved.
- Created technical documentation and collaborated with other developers as needed.

## Udemy | Trainee-FİGMA 2021-2022

- IOS & Android Development Training received.
- Figma Interface Design (UI) Training was received.

## Target-Purpose

- Contributed to frontend projects and collaborated on UI/UX design.
- Developed and styled web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript,React and Typescript.
- Implemented responsive design principles and ensured browser compatibility.
- Incorporated user feedback for improvements and bug fixes.
- Collaborated with project team to deliver projects on time.
- Developed frontend based on project objectives and requirements.
- Designed a user-friendly interface and implemented responsive design.
- Identified technical issues and provided solutions.
- Regularly communicated with the project team to track progress.